All right, and just to wrap up then, I want to say again, this is a very confusing time.
Things are moving so quickly.
Do keep an eye on the documentation.
I'm going to try and make sure that I address things and keep it up to date and look at
the Q and A and you to me.
I'll answer questions and always ask me, try not to get distracted by the noise.
There's so much energy over new announcements that turns out not to be anything.
And so yeah, just don't let that distract you and recognize that the models you use are no
doubt going to be even stronger than the ones I use because new models come out every single week.
So you will get different results. You might get inconsistent results and you might get better
results and you should take joy in that and please share them with me. I love to
hear about it. Put it on the Q&A, share the things that you discover. And
actually on that point it's worth me pointing out that the projects that we
do together in this course, this is very different to all the other courses
I've made, in that there's not going to just be like one bit of code that you run
and you get one result that will match me. Every project is going to be very
different for you and for me.
We're going to get different answers.
And it's like a sort of choose your own adventure thing.
You'll be able to have a lot of flexibility in how you do this.
And you might get very different outcomes.
And that's both really exciting.
It means that you're going to see something unique to you.
It also introduces some challenges because if it doesn't work,
then it's not going to be easy for me to reproduce that.
So we're going to have to figure that out as we go,
but keep that in mind. This is going to be very different to other courses because we're all going
to have slightly different experiences. And look, you've got something else with this package,
something that came with this Udemy course, whether you wanted it or not, it's like a mandatory
extra that comes with it. And that is me. I come with this and I am here to help you.
And as it happens, I actually enjoy helping people.
So you're doing me a favor if you message me.
So at any point, you can hit me up in the Q and A,
you can send me an email, I always reply.
If I don't, then maybe it got in my spam folder
or something, send another email
and I'll definitely reply.
But do that, connect with me on LinkedIn. I love being connected and I love
interacting with people. So take me up on it. Do it. Ask me the questions. And also I encourage
people to post about your learning experience and what you create on LinkedIn. It's a great way
to draw attention to all of the progress you're making and the expertise that you're building.
And if you tag me on your LinkedIn post,
then I'll come in and I'll weigh in and I'll add some comments.
And that's a great way to amplify your accomplishment
and get more visibility to the ways
in which you're building your expertise.
And with that, and with that,
let me show you again the three weeks
to being an expert agentic code at our curriculum.
But now that box on the bottom left, that week one,
day one box, the agent coding landscape, that is filled in to represent that you've
accomplished day one, you've now got a sense of the landscape, the eight stages, the different
tools, whether an ID or a terminal, you've got some of the landscape in mind.
Tomorrow is when we're going to cover the foundations or talk about agents. The agents.md file that is at the heart of all of
this will discuss context overall. But with that, let's celebrate the fact that you're already 7%
complete with this course. I like to do these percentage completes as we go. So you have that
sense of accomplishment with 7% of the way through, which of course means there's 93% of the way left,
but it's going to be a great 93% starting tomorrow with the foundations.
I'll see you then.